Zaki Nusseibeh Collection AD.MC.020
New York University Abu Dhabi Library
Zaki Nusseibeh Collection
1940s-1980s
1970-1980
New York University Abu Dhabi Library
Nusseibeh, Zaki, His Excellency, 1946-
AD.MC.020
149 Photographic Prints
Box 1 - Digital copy only
Content Description
The Zaki Nusseibeh Collection comprises of 149 gelatin silver prints scanned at 400ppi, they are mainly press shots of Sheikh Zayed and Zaki Nusseibeh on numerous state visits including to India, Pakistan, Morocco, France, the USA and UK. There are also some photographs of buildings and streets in Abu Dhabi and Al Ain, the bulk of the images are dated between 1970-1980.
Biographical / Historical
Zaki Nusseibeh was born in Jerusalem, studied there and in Cambridge University, UK, gaining a Masters degree in Economics. He moved to Abu Dhabi in 1967 and became Sheikh Zayed's personal translator in 1968 being bestowed UAE citizenship shortly afterwards.
He has held various positions within the Abu Dhabi government including Director of Information, Director of the Press Office for HH the President, Assistant Minister of Foreign Affairs and International Co-operation and Cultural Advisor at the Ministry of Presidential Affairs, Deputy Chairman of the Abu Dhabi Culture and Heritage Authority, and most recently Minister of State. He has also served on numerous boards, including; Chairman of the London School of Economics LSE Middle East Centre Advisory Board and member of London School of Oriental and African Studies SOAS Middle East Centre Advisory Board, and of the Alliance Française Foundation in Paris. He was also the President of the Alliance Francaise Abu Dhabi and the UAE chapter of the International 'Friends of Richard Wagner' society. He helped in founding the Abu Dhabi Classics program in Abu Dhabi and the Al Ain Music Festival in Al Ain. In 2014 he was also asked to chair the Wagner Foundation in Leipzig, Germany and is a member on the Board of Trustees of the Agha Khan Museum in Toronto and of the Institut du Monde Arabe in Paris.
- A mosque in Abu Dhabi., Circa 1970; ref1; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Architecture; Islamic Architecture; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Mosques; Gelatin Silver Prints; Religious Sites; Photographic Prints
- A group performing Al Ayala traditional dance., Circa 1970; ref2; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Traditional Dress; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Police; Dancing; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Men; Girls; Audiences/Spectators; Canes/Walking Sticks; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Weapons; Guns; Outdoors
- Clock Tower roundabout on Corniche Street., Circa 1970; ref3; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Buildings; Architecture; Cars; Streets/Roads; Clocks/Watches; Towers; Corniche; Boats/Ships; Street Lamps
- Trucks at a loading dock at the Abu Dhabi port., Circa 1970; ref4; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Trucks; Ports; Boats/Ships; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Transportation; Outdoors
- Boats on a coastline., Circa 1970; ref5; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Boats/Ships; Men; Water; Coast; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Transportation; Persian Gulf; Outdoors
- Rolls Royce belonging to Sheikh Zayed in downtown Abu Dhabi., Circa 1970; ref6; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Streets/Roads; Cars; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Buildings; Architecture; Transportation
- Gardeners in a park., Circa 1970; ref7; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Water; Gardens; Workers; Parks; Men; Street Lamps; Outdoors
- Minaret of Shiekh Zayed the Second Mosque in Abu Dhabi., Circa 1970; ref8; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Mosques; Islamic Architecture; Buildings; Architecture
- Scaffolding surrounding a street light on Corniche road., Circa 1970; ref9; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Corniche; Flags; Street Lamps; Streets/Roads; Men; Buildings; Workers; Outdoors
- A street view with an open air cinema building in the background., Circa 1970; ref10; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Streets/Roads; Street Lamps; Cars; Buildings; Cinema; Transportation; Signs/Signposts; Advertisements
- Souq Al Markezi in Abu Dhabi., Circa 1970; ref11; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Signs/Signposts; Shops; Markets; Men; Buildings; Traditional Dress; Crowds; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Arabic Writing; English Writing; Flags; Outdoors
- Street photographer with a wet process camera., Circa 1970s; ref12; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Streets/Roads; Men; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Cameras; Street Vendors; Outdoors
- A street view with the Grindlays Bank building in front., Circa 1970s; ref13; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Streets/Roads; Street Lamps; Signs/Signposts; Street Signs; Shops; Architecture; Buildings; Cars; Banks; Flags
- Al Fahim mosque at the junction of the roads then known as Khalifa Street, Al Istiqlal Street and Airport Road., Circa 1970s; ref14; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Architecture; Islamic Architecture; Mosques; Buildings; Streets/Roads; Men; Arabic Calligraphy; Shops
- Two boys riding a horse and a boy walking with them., Circa 1970s; ref15; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Boys; Horses; Animals; Deserts; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Traditional Dress; Outdoors
- Men walking on the side of the Corniche., Circa 1970s; ref16; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Corniche; Coast; Men; Canes/Walking Sticks; Water; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Persian Gulf; Outdoors
- Central Abu Dhabi, Sheikh Hamdan Street., Circa 1970s; ref17; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Streets/Roads; Cars; Street Lamps; Signs/Signposts; Architecture; Buildings; Transportation; Shops
- A woman carrying a basket on her head., Circa 1970s; ref18; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Trucks; Women; Men; Traditional Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Machines; Outdoors
- A wind tower., Circa 1970s; ref19; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Towers; Architecture; Buildings
- National Bank of Abu Dhabi on Khalifa street., Circa 1970s; ref20; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Banks; Buildings; Architecture; Cars; Flags; Signs/Signposts; Transportation
- Energy plant in Al Khalidiya., Circa 1970s; ref21; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Factory; Construction; Street Lamps; Buildings
- Portrait of Sheikh Zayed., Circa 1970s; ref22; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Individual Portraits; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Sheikhs; Political Leadership; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb
- A gravel depot with trucks in the background., Circa 1970s; ref23; 1 Photographic Prints 22.2 x 30 cm (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Trucks; Workers; Men; Transportation; Outdoors
- Street view with Rolls Royce belonging to Sheikh Zayed., Circa 1970s; ref24; 1 Photographic Prints 21 x 29.7 cm (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Streets/Roads; Cars; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Signs/Signposts; Architecture; Buildings; Transportation; Street Lamps
- Kentucky Fried Chicken and Wimpy building next to Al Bateen Airport., Circa 1970s; ref25; 1 Photographic Prints 22.2 x 29.6 cm (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Restaurants; Street Lamps; Parks; Signs/Signposts; Streets/Roads; Architecture; Buildings; Restaurants; Arabic Writing; English Writing
- A man standing on a concrete wall., Circa 1970s; ref26; 1 Photographic Prints 22.3 x 30 cm (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Trucks; Men; Ports; Construction; Transportation; Outdoors
- People at the Corniche., Circa 1970s; ref27; 1 Photographic Prints 21.7 x 30.4 cm (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Corniche; Men; Children; Boys; Girls; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Water; Persian Gulf; Outdoors
- Al Ain during the union with the Clock Tower in the background., Circa 1970s; ref28; 1 Photographic Prints 21.1 x 29.7 cm (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Clocks/Watches; Monuments; Al Ain, UAE; Buildings; Street Signs; Street Lamps; Streets/Roads
- Hilton Al Ain with tents in the foreground., Circa 1970s; ref29; 1 Photographic Prints 21 x 29.5 cm (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Al Ain, UAE; Hotels; Tents; Buildings; Architecture; Street Lamps; Electricity
- Picture of Zayed Port taken from motor boat., Circa 1970s; ref30; 1 Photographic Prints 22.1 x 29.9 cm (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Water; Persian Gulf; Boats/Ships; Men; Ports; Transportation
- Helicopter at Hilton Al Ain., Circa 1970s; ref31; 1 Photographic Prints 22.3 x 29.9 cm (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Al Ain, UAE; Hotels; Transportation; Cars; Airplanes; Buildings; Architecture
- An abacus in a classroom., Circa 1970s; ref32; 1 Photographic Prints 21.1 x 29.6 cm (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Classrooms; Children; Girls; Uniforms; Pens/Inkwells; Schools/Education
- Central Abu Dhabi with the Banque de Paris et des Paybas and Mohammed Rasool Khoury & Sons buildings on Airport road., Circa 1970; ref33; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Streets/Roads; Street Lamps; Cars; Signs/Signposts; Buildings; Architecture; Construction; Banks; Shops; Transportation; Advertisements; English Writing
- Falcon statue., Circa 1970; ref34; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Statues; Buildings; Arabic Writing
- Qasr Al Hosn., Circa 1970; ref35; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Architecture; Buildings; Forts/Castles
- Khalidiya Palace Hotel., Circa 1970; ref36; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Architecture; Buildings; Street Lamps; Hotels; Irrigation system
- View of Hamdan Street., Circa 1970; ref37; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Street Signs; Streets/Roads; Street Lamps; Men; Buildings; Construction; Architecture; Cars; Transportation; Flags; Outdoors
- An external view of stables with horses., Circa 1970; ref38; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Buildings; Architecture; Horses; Deserts; Animals
- Zaki Nusseibeh by Rene Burri., 20 October 1974; ref39; Burri, René, 1933-2014; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Telephones; Individual Portraits; French Writing; Furnishings; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Offices
- Portrait of Zaki Nusseibeh., Circa 1970; ref40; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Individual Portraits; Men
- Abu Dhabi Police headquarters opposite of Qasr Al Hosn., Circa 1970; ref41; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Cars; Men; Uniforms; Weapons; Guns; Buildings; Police; Traditional Dress; Transportation; Outdoors; Canes/Walking Sticks
- Zaki Nusseibeh working on an airplane., Circa 1970; ref42; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Men; Airplanes; Transportation; Pens/Inkwells; Clocks/Watches
- Studio portrait of young Zaki Nusseibeh holding a camera with a child., Circa 1950; ref43; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Group Portraits; Studio Photography; Children; Boys; Cameras
- A studio portrait of a young Zaki Nusseibeh., Circa 1950; ref44; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- Sheikh Zayed shaking hands with Zaki Nusseibeh., Circa 1970; ref45; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Men; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Traditional Dress; Uniforms; Police; Political Leadership
- Five men with rifles seated on a sofa., Circa 1970; ref46; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Guns; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Weapons; Furnishings
- Sheikh Zayed seated in a gathering., Circa 1970; ref47; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Audiences/Spectators; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Men; Binoculars; Women; Political Leadership
- Portrait of Zaki Nusseibeh., Circa 1970; ref48; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Men; Individual Portraits; Pens/Inkwells; Offices
- Sheikh Zayed and a group of men in front of Al Bateen Airport., Circa 1970; ref50; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Airports; Men; Cars; Flags; Buildings; Uniforms; Police; Trucks; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Transportation; Arabic Writing; English Writing; Outdoors; Political Leadership
- Zaki Nusseibeh sitting at a desk., Circa 1970; ref51; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Individual Portraits; Offices; Cigarettes; Offices; Telephones; Furnishings; Newspapers/Magazines
- A studio portrait of a young Zaki Nusseibeh., Circa 1950; ref52; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Unknown Locations; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography
- Abu Dhabi Police band in Qasr Al Hosn., 1963; ref53; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Boys; Crowds; Uniforms; Marching Band; Police; Forts/Castles; Architecture; Buildings; Arabic Writing; Outdoors
- Group portrait of the First Abu Dhabi Police Band., 1963; ref54; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Group Portraits; Police; Uniforms; Marching Band; Arabic Writing
- Boats at the Dubai creek., Circa 1970; ref55; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Dubai, United Arab Emirates; Boats/Ships; Water; Cars; Streets/Roads; Buildings; Construction; Men; Transportation
- A view of oil drilling rig from below., Circa 1970; ref56; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Machines
- A ferris wheel with a portrait of Sheikh Zayed in the middle., Circa 1970; ref57; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Individual Portraits; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Arabic Writing; Paintings
- Sheikh Zayed with British Prime Minister Margaret Thatcher and Zaki Nusseibeh during her visit to UAE., 1981; ref58; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; United Arab Emirates; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Men; Women; Uniforms; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Political Leadership; Military/Soldiers; Gloves; Bags/Purses; Jewelry; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- Sheikh Khalifa with Queen Elizabeth and Zaki Nusseibeh., Circa 1970; ref59; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Women; Royalty; Sheikhs; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Political Leadership; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Gloves; Hats; Bags/Purses; Outdoors
- Princess Diana and Prince Charles in the UAE seating next to Sheikh Nahyan bin Mubarak and Sheikh Tahnoon bin Mohammed Al Nahyan., 1989; ref60; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Women; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Royalty; Crowds; Sheikhs; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Shoes/Boots; Televisions; Furnishings; Fruit/Vegetables
- Princess Diana and Zaki Nusseibeh., 1989; ref61; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Color Photography; Men; Women; Royalty; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Traditional Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Jewelry; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- Princess Diana, Prince Charles, Sheikh Tahnoon bin Mohammed Al Nahyan, Sheikh Nahyan bin Mubarak Al Nahyan and Zaki Nusseibeh., 1989; ref62; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Women; Crowds; Cars; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Royalty; Sheikhs; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Police; Transportation; Outdoors
- Sheikh Zayed with Prince Charles and Princess Diana and Zaki Nusseibeh., 1989; ref63; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Color Photography; Women; Men; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Royalty; Weapons; Guns; Hats; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Bags/Purses; Political Leadership
- Sheikh Khalifa with Prince Charles and Zaki Nusseibeh on the occasion of The Queen's Diamond Jubilee., 2012; ref64; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Chandeliers; London, United Kingdom; Royalty; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Men; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Color Photography; Furnishings; Political Leadership
- Sheikh Zayed with Prince Charles and Princess Diana on a red carpet with Zaki Nusseibeh., 1989; ref65; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Women; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Royalty; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Hats; Bags/Purses; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Weapons; Guns
- Sheikh Zayed walking with Queen Elizabeth and Zaki Nusseibeh., 1979; ref66; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Women; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Royalty; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Canes/Walking Sticks; Political Leadership; Outdoors
- Sheikh Zayed, Queen Elizabeth and Zaki Nussiebeh at a dinner hosted by Sheikh Zayed in honor of Queen Elizabeth at Claridge Hotel., 1989; ref67; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; London, United Kingdom; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Royalty; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Men; Women; Medals; Jewelry; Hotels; Political Leadership
- Sheikh Zayed walking with Queen Elizabeth and Zaki Nusseibeh., 1979; ref68; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Men; Women; Royalty; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Hats; Gloves; Bags/Purses; Political Leadership
- Sheikh Zayed, Sheikh Rashid bin Saeed Al Maktoum and Zaki Nusseibeh with British Prime Minister Margaret Thatcher., 1981; ref69; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; United Arab Emirates; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Sheikhs; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Men; Women; Political Leadership
- Sheikh Zayed and Queen Elizabeth, with Prince Philip, Sheikh Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum and Zaki Nusseibeh., 1989; ref70; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; London, United Kingdom; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Sheikhs; Color Photography; Men; Women; Royalty; Uniforms; Cars; Palace; Political Leadership
- Sheikh Khalifa and Prince Charles holding a gift with Zaki Nusseibeh and Ahmed Jumaa Al Zaabi., 1989; ref71; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Sheikhs; Men; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Insignia/Emblem; Political Leadership
- Sheikh Khalifa with Prince Charles walking on a deck of the Royal Yacht Britannia with Sheikh Mohammed bin Zayed and Zaki Nusseibeh in the background., 1989; ref72; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Sheikhs; Men; Color Photography; Boats/Ships; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb; Bow Ties; Political Leadership; Transportation
- Sheikh Zayed and Zaki Nusseibeh greeting British Prime Minister Margaret Thatcher during her visit to UAE., 1981; ref73; 1 Photographic Prints (Box 1 - Digital copy only)
  Photographic Prints; Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates; Men; Women; Color Photography; Cars; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Political Leadership; Transportation; Traditional Dress; Kandora/Dishdasha/Thawb